[{"stepName": "Identify Motion of objects", "stepNumber": 1, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "How many moving objects are present?", "options": [5, 1, 2, 3], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "show1": [""], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "How many strings are there?", "options": [4, 1, 3, 2], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "showfc": []}, {"question": "How many contacting surfaces are there?", "options": [0, 3, 1, 4], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "showfc": []}]}, {"stepName": "Write FBD equation for each Moving block", "stepNumber": 2, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "How many surfaces are in contact with the red block?", "options": [0, 4, 3, 1], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -200, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "answer": 3, "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 1 due to B?", "options": ["N1perpendicular up", "N1perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "answer": 0, "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for red block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on red block?", "options": ["T\u2081 rightwards", "T\u2081 leftwards"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2081+30=0", "-N\u2081+30=0", "+N\u2081-30=0", "-N\u2081-30=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: 30", "Rightward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Leftward Forces: "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the x-direction", "options": ["+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0"], "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: 30", "Rightward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Leftward Forces: "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for yellow block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "showfc": ["Yellow block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on yellow block?", "options": ["T\u2082 downwards", "T\u2082 upwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "showfc": ["Yellow block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+40+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-40+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "showfc": ["Yellow block", "Upward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Downward Forces: 40", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for first pulley cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["First pulley", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "answer": 3}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on first pulley?", "options": ["T\u2081 leftwards", "T\u2081 rightwards"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["First pulley", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on first pulley?", "options": ["T\u2081 rightwards", "T\u2081 leftwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["First pulley", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2081, "]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on first pulley?", "options": ["T\u2082 leftwards", "T\u2082 rightwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 3, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["First pulley", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2081, T\u2081, "]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of first pulley in the x-direction", "options": ["+2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["First pulley", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2081, T\u2081, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"]}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Understanding", "stepNumber": 3, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string if the dog is moving towards right with speed 5 m/s", "options": [5, -5], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": [0, 5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string is 5 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string if the dog is moving towards left with speed 5 m/s", "options": [5, -5], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": [0, -5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string is -5 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string if the human is moving towards right with speed 3 m/s", "options": [-3, 3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": [3, 0], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string is -3 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string if the human is moving towards left with speed 3 m/s", "options": [3, -3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, 0], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string is 3 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of dog in right direction with speed 5 m/s", "options": [5, -5], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 5, "threejssubsubstep": [3, 5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of human in right direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [-3, 3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 6, "threejssubsubstep": [3, 5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "Net rate of change of length due to dog moving towards right direction with speed 5 m/s  and human moving in right direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [2, -2, -8, 8], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 7, "threejssubsubstep": [3, 5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s", "Total Rate of change of length of the string due motion of both human and dog is 2m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of dog in right direction with speed 5 m/s", "options": [5, -5], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 8, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, 5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of human in left direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [3, -3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 9, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, 5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "Net rate of change of length due to dog moving towards right direction with speed 5 m/s  and human moving in left direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [2, -2, -8, 8], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 10, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, 5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s", "Total Rate of change of length of the string due motion of both human and dog is 8m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of dog in left direction with speed 5 m/s", "options": [-5, 5], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 11, "threejssubsubstep": [3, -5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of human in right direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [-3, 3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 12, "threejssubsubstep": [3, -5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "Net rate of change of length due to dog moving towards left direction with speed 5 m/s  and human moving in right direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [8, -8, -2, 2], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 13, "threejssubsubstep": [3, -5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s", "Total Rate of change of length of the string due motion of both human and dog is -8m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of dog in left direction with speed 5 m/s", "options": [5, -5], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 14, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, -5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of human in left direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [3, -3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 15, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, -5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "Net rate of change of length due to dog moving towards left direction with speed 5 m/s  and human moving in left direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [-2, 2, 8, -8], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 16, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, -5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s", "Total Rate of change of length of the string due motion of both human and dog is -2m/s"], "showfc": []}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Equations", "stepNumber": 4, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What is the number of parts which change length in the pink string?", "options": [5, 4, 2, 3], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:", "options": ["+a\u2083", "-a\u2083"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": ["Pink string", "l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"]}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:", "options": ["+a\u2081", "-a\u2081"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": ["Pink string", "l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"]}, {"question": "What is net double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:", "options": ["+a\u2083+a\u2081", "+a\u2083-a\u2081", "-a\u2083+a\u2081", "-a\u2083-a\u2081"], "answer": [1], "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": ["Pink string", "l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"]}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2082 for pink string:", "options": ["+a\u2083", "-a\u2083"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": ["Pink string", "l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"]}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for pink string?", "options": ["+a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "+a\u2081x-2.0a\u2083=0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "-a\u2081x-2.0a\u2083=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "showfc": ["Pink string", "l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant", "l\u2081'' = +a\u2083-a\u2081", "l\u2082'' = +a\u2083"]}, {"question": "What is the number of parts which change length in the red string?", "options": [5, 4, 2, 3], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "showfc": []}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for red string:", "options": ["+a\u2083", "-a\u2083"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "showfc": ["Red string", "l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"]}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2082 for red string:", "options": ["+a\u2082", "-a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "showfc": ["Red string", "l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"]}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for red string?", "options": ["+a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "showfc": ["Red string", "l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant", "l\u2081'' = -a\u2083", "l\u2082'' = +a\u2082"]}]}]